Finding Aid for the Music Department Photograph Collection, circa 1920-2008
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Photographs, circa 1920-2008, I.
  - Jerry Kirkbride, clarinetist performing with string quartet, including Jesse Levine, 2/28/1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 5, Item MD05-029)
  - Donald Knaack, percussionist behind glass chimes, 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-030)
  - Donald Knaack, percussionist in recording session, 1975-1976, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-031)
  - Jo Kondo, composer, 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-032)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-033)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist with Eberhard Blum and Jay Hersher, February 15 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-034)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist, performing with Creative Associates, Spring 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Kirstein, Edward (Box 5, Item MD05-035)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist with Creative Associates performing at conference, Spring 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Kirstein, Edward (Box 5, Item MD05-036)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist with Creative Associates performing at conference, Spring 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Kirstein, Edward (Box 5, Item MD05-037)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist with Creative Associates performing at conference, Spring 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Kirstein, Edward (Box 5, Item MD05-038)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist rehearsing with Creative Associates, 1971-1972, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 5, Item MD05-039)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist rehearsing with Mark Sokol on stage, 1970-1971, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-040)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist rehearsing with Creative Associates at conference, Spring 1973, 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Kirstein, Edward (Box 5, Item MD05-041)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist rehearsing with Creative Associates, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 5, Item MD05-042)
  - Petr Kotík, flutist with Roberto Laneri by window, 1971-1972, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 5, Item MD05-043)
  - Jeffery Kowalsky, percussionist with Creative Associates performing at conference, Spring 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Kirstein, Edward (Box 5, Item MD05-044)
  - Karl Kraber, flutist seated, holding a piccolo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-045)
  - Karl Kraber, flutist seated, holding a piccolo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-046)
  - Karl Kraber, flutist with Paolo Dimiziani, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-047)
  - Ernst Krenek, composer conducting University at Buffalo Wind Ensemble, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-048)
  - Joseph Kubera, pianist with fire extinguisher crouching near piano, 1975-1976, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-049)
  - David Kuehn, trumpet player, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-050)
  - Joan La Barbara, composer on stage with Creative Associates, February 13 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-051)
  - Joan La Barbara, composer singing with Creative Associates, February 13 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-052)
  - Roberto Laneri, clarinetist with Creative Associates, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 5, Item MD05-053)
  - Joelle Leandre, double bassist wearing sunglasses, Fall 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Seman, David (Box 5, Item MD05-054)
  - Joelle Leandre, double bassist playing outdoors, 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Le Anh, Claude (Box 5, Item MD05-055)
  - Joelle Leandre, double bassist rehearsing with 2 percussionists (contact sheet), undated, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-056)
  - Renée Levine, administrator, December 19 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-057)
  - Renée Levine, administrator, December 19 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-058)
  - Renée Levine, administrator, looking towards her right, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-059)
  - Renée Levine, administrator, looking towards her right, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-060)
  - Renée Levine, administrator, looking towards her right, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-061)
  - Renée Levine, administrator, looking towards her right, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-062)
  - Renée Levine, administrator at table, speaking into microphone sitting between 2 unidentified men, October 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Rusiniak, Chris (Box 5, Item MD05-063)
  - Renée Levine, administrator with Carol Plantamura, Sylvia Dimiziani, and Diane Williams, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-064)
  - Renée Levine, administrator with Carol Plantamura, Sylvia Dimiziani, and Diane Williams, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-065)
  - Arie Lipsky, violoncellist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-066)
  - Garrett List, trombonist conducting Creative Associates, Fall 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Rusiniak, Chris (Box 5, Item MD05-067)
  - Alvin Lucier, composer, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Lucier, Mary (Box 5, Item MD05-068)
  - Stephen Manes, pianist with unidentified student, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-069)
  - Stephen Manes, pianist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Schaaf, Peter (Box 5, Item MD05-070)
  - Judith Lynn Martin, composer, 1974-1975, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-071)
  - Judith Lynn Martin, composer demonstrating electronic equipment outdoors, June 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-072)
  - Judith Lynn Martin, composer demonstrating electronic equipment outdoors, June 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-073)
  - Judith Lynn Martin, composer demonstrating electronic equipment outdoors, June 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-074)
  - Robert Lazarus Martin, violoncellist performing at Evenings for New Music, 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 5, Item MD05-075)
  - Robert Lazarus Martin, violoncellist performing at Evenings for New Music, 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 5, Item MD05-076)
  - Robert Lazarus Martin, violoncellist performing at Evenings for New Music, 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 5, Item MD05-077)
  - James W. McKinnon, faculty being presented with award, 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-078)
  - James W. McKinnon, faculty being presented with award, 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-079)
  - James W. McKinnon, faculty being presented with award, 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-080)
  - Makoto Michii, double bassist performing with Creative Associates, March 5 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-001)
  - Makoto Michii, double bassist performing, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-002)
  - Makoto Michii, double bassist performing, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-003)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, pianist leaning on side of piano, 1979, 1 black and white photograph; Miles, Joann (Box 6, Item MD06-004)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, pianist seated at piano, 1979, 1 black and white photograph; Miles, Joann (Box 6, Item MD06-005)
  - M.I.T., sound-proofed room, May 1975, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-006)
  - Donald G. Miller, trombonist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-007)
  - Nicolas Molfese, double bassist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-008)
  - Robert W. Mols, flutist wearing all black, seated, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-009)
  - Robert W. Mols, flutist playing piccolo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-010)
  - Robert Morris, composer working with Aki Takahashi (contact sheet), undated, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-011)
  - Richard Myers, trombonist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Ettore-Winter (Buffalo) (Box 6, Item MD06-012)
  - Richard Myers, trombonist working with unidentified student, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-013)
  - Fredric Myrow, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-014)
  - Fredric Myrow, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-015)
  - Fredric Myrow, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-016)
  - Fredric Myrow, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-017)
  - Buell Neidlinger, double bassist, 1964-1965, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-018)
  - Buell Neidlinger, double bassist playing, 1964-1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 6, Item MD06-019)
  - John Newell, composer conducting Creative Associates, May 1 1976, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 6, Item MD06-020)
  - John Newell, composer conducting Creative Associates, May 1 1976, 1 black and white photograph; Rusiniak, Chris (Box 6, Item MD06-021)
  - John Newell, composer conducting Creative Associates, May 1 1976, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 6, Item MD06-022)
  - John Newell, composer conducting Creative Associates (contact sheet), May 1 1976, 1 black and white contact sheet; Rusiniak, Chris (Box 6, Item MD06-023)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-024)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-025)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-026)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-027)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-028)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-029)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-030)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-031)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-032)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-033)
  - New Percussion Quartet, 1/31/1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-034)
  - New Percussion Quartet, 1/31/1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-035)
  - New Percussion Quartet, 1/31/1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-036)
  - Orford String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-037)
  - Orford String Quartet, 1988, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-038)
  - Orford String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-039)
  - Orford String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Taillefer, R. Eugene (Box 6, Item MD06-040)
  - Orford String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Taillefer, R. Eugene (Box 6, Item MD06-041)
  - Orford String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-042)
  - Michael Peebles, violoncellist, Spring 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-043)
  - Charles Peltz, conductor in performance, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-044)
  - Charles Peltz, conductor in rehearsal, September 23 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Walion, Robert (Box 6, Item MD06-045)
  - Charles Peltz, conductor in rehearsal, September 23 1986, 1 black and white photograph; Walion, Robert (Box 6, Item MD06-046)
  - Charles Peltz, conductor in rehearsal, September 16 1986, 1 black and white photograph; Specker, Francis (Box 6, Item MD06-047)
  - Charles Peltz, conductor in rehearsal, September 16 1986, 1 black and white photograph; Specker, Francis (Box 6, Item MD06-048)
  - Charles Peltz, conductor in rehearsal, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-049)
  - Charles Peltz, conductor in rehearsal, September 16 1986, 1 black and white photograph; Specker, Francis (Box 6, Item MD06-050)
  - Charles Peltz, conductor in performance, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-051)
  - Charles Peltz, conductor in rehearsal, September 16 1986, 1 black and white photograph; Specker, Francis (Box 6, Item MD06-052)
  - Carlo Pinto, pianist, 6/21/1984, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 6, Item MD06-053)
  - Carol Plantamura, vocalist seated with Creative Associates, 1964-1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 6, Item MD06-054)
  - Carol Plantamura, vocalist seated with Creative Associates, 1964-1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 6, Item MD06-055)
  - Carol Plantamura, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-056)
  - Carol Plantamura, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-057)
  - Carol Plantamura, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-058)
  - Carol Plantamura, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-059)
  - Carol Plantamura, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-060)
  - Carol Plantamura, vocalist eating at reception, 1964-1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 6, Item MD06-061)
  - Nora Post, oboist sitting on a rock, 1975-1976, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 6, Item MD06-062)
  - Nora Post, oboist rehearsing with other musicians (contact sheet), 1977-1978, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-063)
  - Nora Post, oboist outdoors with Creative Associates, 1977-1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-064)
  - Nora Post, oboist rehearsing with Creative Associates, 1975-1976, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 6, Item MD06-065)
  - Nora Post, oboist rehearsing with Creative Associates (contact sheet), 1977-1978, 1 black and white contact sheet; Seman, David (Box 6, Item MD06-066)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-067)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer conducting Creative Associates, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-068)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer conducting Creative Associates, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-069)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer conducting Creative Associates, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-070)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer conducting Creative Associates, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-071)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer standing with other musicians, March 17 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-072)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer conducting, March 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-073)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer conducting Creative Associates in his opera, Votre Faust, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-074)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer conducting Creative Associates in his opera, Votre Faust, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-075)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer with Michel Butor, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-076)
  - Henri Pousseur, composer with Michel Butor and Creative Associates, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-077)
  - One page of the score to Henri Pousseur's Votre Faust, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-078)
  - One page of the score to Henri Pousseur's Votre Faust, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 6, Item MD06-079)
  - James Pyne, clarinetist holding instrument, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item MD06-081)
  - Heinz Rehfuss, vocalist accompanied by Carlo Pinto, October 1 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 7, Item MD07-001)
  - Heinz Rehfuss, vocalist (baritone) at piano with unidentified student (standing), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-002)
  - Roger Reynolds, composer with Diane Williams and Jan Williams, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-003)
  - Ronald Richards, oboist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-004)
  - Terry Riley, composer, June 3 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 7, Item MD07-005)
  - George Ritscher, audio technician/electronicist, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 7, Item MD07-006)
  - George Rochberg, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-007)
  - George Rochberg, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-008)
  - Carlos Roqué Alsina, composer conducting Creative Associates, March 10 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 7, Item MD07-009)
  - Carlos Roqué Alsina, composer conducting Creative Associates, March 10 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 7, Item MD07-010)
  - Carlos Roqué Alsina, composer conducting Creative Associates, March 10 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 7, Item MD07-011)
  - Carlos Roqué Alsina, composer conducting Creative Associates, March 10 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 7, Item MD07-012)
  - Ned Rorem, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-013)
  - Maria Runfola, faculty (music education), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-014)
  - Frederic Rzewski, composer with Stephen Manes, Ralph Jones, and Benjamin Hudson onstage, 1973-1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-015)
  - Michael Sahl, pianist with students seated in semi-circle, February 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 7, Item MD07-016)
  - Allen Sapp, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-017)
  - Allen Sapp, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-018)
  - Allen Sapp, composer seated at piano with Ned Rorem and 1 unidentified man looking on, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-019)
  - Allen Sapp, composer accepting award on behalf of Music Department, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-020)
  - Allen Sapp, composer accepting award on behalf of Music Department (contact sheet), 1964, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-021)
  - Allen Sapp, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-022)
  - Allen Sapp, composer watching Creative Associates perform, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Kirstein, Edward (Box 7, Item MD07-023)
  - Allen Sapp, composer looking over balcony, 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 7, Item MD07-024)
  - Allen Sapp, composer looking over balcony, 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 7, Item MD07-025)
  - Allen Sapp, composer at award ceremony with other Buffalo musicians, May 14 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Fredericks, Michael Jr (Box 7, Item MD07-026)
  - Allen Sapp, composer at award ceremony with other Buffalo musicians, May 14 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Fredericks, Michael Jr (Box 7, Item MD07-027)
  - Paul Schmidt, vocalist accompanied by Yvar Mikhashoff, March 18 1988, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-028)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, seated at edge of stage, 1971-1972, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 7, Item MD07-029)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, seated at edge of stage, 1971-1972, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 7, Item MD07-030)
  - Sequoia String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-031)
  - Lowell E. Shaw, horn player, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-032)
  - Roger Shields, pianist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 7, Item MD07-033)
  - Allen Sigel, clarinetist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-034)
  - Allen Sigel, clarinetist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-035)
  - Allen Sigel, clarinetist performing with Leo Smit and Pamela Benjamin Adelstein (Pamela McConnell), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-036)
  - Allen Sigel, clarinetist with Ronald Richards and other woodwind players (unidentified), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-037)
  - Jill Simon, outdoors (profile), June 1965, 1 color photograph; Dursie, Tom (Box 7, Item MD07-038)
  - Harriet Simons, conductor discussing score with vocalists, March 14 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-039)
  - Harriet Simons, conductor rehearsing University at Buffalo Choir, May 23 1980, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-040)
  - Harriet Simons, conductor rehearsing University at Buffalo Choir, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-041)
  - Harriet Simons, conductor rehearsing, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-042)
  - Harriet Simons, conductor, October 9 1986, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-043)
  - Harriet Simons, conductor with University at Buffalo Choir in performance, April 12 1990, 1 black and white photograph; Hill, Debbie (Box 7, Item MD07-044)
  - Harriet Simons, conductor with European tour University at Buffalo Choir members, October 26 1994, 1 black and white photograph; Andrusz, Marlene (Box 7, Item MD07-045)
  - Harriet Simons, conductor with University at Buffalo Choir receiving applause, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 7, Item MD07-046)